ecollectionsetc.com 2016-04-20

# Privacy Policy: Customer Information - Shop Justice

PRIVACY POLICY 

Updated and effective as of April 14, 2016.

We are committed to protecting your personal information. Please take a few minutes to read and understand our privacy policies so that you know how we collect, use and share your personal information obtained online and in our U.S. stores. This Privacy Policy supersedes any prior privacy policy, statements, or representations relating to the collection, retention, or sharing of information.

Our site is intended for a general audience and we do not knowingly collect personal information online from children under the age of 13 unless doing so is in compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act.

### Contents

  * Collection of Customer Information
  * Information Collected for the Purpose of Online Orders
  * The Use of Cookies and Similar Tracking Technologies
  * How Your Information is Used and Shared
  * Online Advertising, Third Party Advertisers and Analytics
  * How We Respond To “Do Not Track” Signals
  * Information You Disclose Publicly on our Sites
  * Information We Receive from Third Parties
  * Contracted Companies that Facilitate Communications and Transactions With You
  * Disclosure Required by Law and to Help Protect the Security and Safety of Our Websites
  * Choices You Have About the Collection, Use and Sharing of your Personal Information
  * California Residents
  * Privacy Policy Questions
  * Security of Our Website

### 1\. Collection of Customer Information.

Justice collects various types of personal information about you during the course of our customer relationship. We do not require you to share any personal information in order to enjoy our website or purchase items in our stores. However, our site may contain special sections and privileges for members who register. Details on the information we ask for at registration, as well as any other rules or restrictions, are made available at registration areas.

The personal information we ask for online is usually first and last name, mailing address, phone number and email address. We do not collect any personal information online unless it is voluntarily provided, for instance when registering, participating in contests, sweepstakes, promotions, completing online surveys, creating a wishlist and emailing it to a friend, or purchasing products from our online stores.

We also collect information from you offline if, for example, you request a copy of our catalog, participate in a sweepstakes or purchase products from one of our stores. Justice also collects aggregate, non-personal information that is used to help us improve your customer experience. We may combine this information with information we collect on or offline to better understand your needs, target advertising to you, and to improve our stores, websites, products and services.

### 2\. Information Collected for the Purpose of Online Orders.

Online shoppers at shopjustice.com must be over age 18 and must use a valid credit card or other valid payment method accepted by us to purchase products online. Visitors younger than 18 may make a Wishlist. When an online order is placed, we collect information associated with the requested transaction, such as the customer's name, mailing address, products ordered, shipping addresses, email address, and credit card information. We ask for this information so that we may fulfill the order. We will send a confirmation email to the address provided after the order is successfully placed. Customers will be added to our marketing database unless they have requested not to receive such communications by opting-out.

You have the option of registering certain information for future orders while completing your online order. If you choose to register, we will capture your login name, password, name and mailing address, and any alternate ship-to addresses. Once you have successfully entered the required information, an account will be created for you online.

### 3\. The Use of Cookies and Similar Tracking Technologies.

A "cookie" is a small file that is saved on a user's hard drive. Shopjustice.com uses cookies and similar passive tracking devices to determine how many people visit our websites, which web pages are visited, how long visitors stay there and the amount of the purchase. This information helps us create a better website experience and provide you with targeted advertising. We also may use 1x1 pixels (“clear gifs” or “web beacons”), embedded scripts or similar technologies to automatically collect certain non-personal information related to your use of our website, such as your browser, the time of day you visit our site, all the content you view, and the type of device you are using to access our website.

Each visitor's IP address may also be collected. An IP address is the automatic number assigned to each user's computer when that person surfs the web.

If you access our content via a mobile device, we may also receive your mobile device identifier. Some mobile service providers may also provide with information regarding the physical location of the device used to access our content.

### 4\. How Your Information is Used and Shared.

Tween Brands, owner of the Justice brand, may share personally identifiable information collected online and in-store under this Privacy Policy with and among its affiliated companies, including other brands owned by Tween Brands' parent company, Ascena Retail Group, Inc., for several purposes. For example, your personal information may be used to send you promotional materials about goods and services (including special offers and promotions) either offered by Justice or other Ascena-owned brands. We may also send you promotional materials about goods or services offered by outside third parties. These promotional materials may be sent to you by postal mail, email or other means. You may opt-out of receiving these communications. Please note that when you purchase or request products from Justice promotional materials may accompany delivery of that product. We refer to sending you promotional materials in these circumstances as "fulfillment uses" of your personal information. Because these promotional materials accompany products that you have requested, your opt-outs, if any, will not apply to any of these fulfillment uses.

Justice may also use your personal information for purposes other than sending you promotional materials. For example, we may use your information to complete transactions requested by you (such as your purchase of a product offered on one of our websites), or to send you administrative communications about either your account with us or new features on our websites, including any future changes to this Privacy Policy. Because these uses of your personal information do not involve sending you promotional materials, your opt-outs will not apply to any of these operational uses.

In addition, there may be times when, at your direction, we will share certain information with a third party website, such as if you choose to post content from one of our sites or online features to your personal page on another website or if you log-in to our site using your credentials from another website. In those cases, we will share the information necessary to carry out your request.

We may take your personally identifiable information and make it non-personally identifiable, either by combining it with information about other individuals (aggregating for example your age and gender or similar information with information about other individuals), and/or by removing characteristics (such as your name) that make the information personally identifiable directly to you. Given the nature of this information, there are no restrictions under this Privacy Policy upon our right to aggregate or de-personalize your personal information and we may use, sell and/or share such non-personally identifiable information with any outside third parties.

From time to time we may release your personal information to select third parties so that they (or their clients/subscribers) can send you promotional materials and communications about respective goods and services ("promotional purposes") offered by them. When releasing your information for promotional purposes, we attempt to select reputable companies that offer high quality products and services. However, your personal information will become permanently subject to the information use and release practices of that third party. Those parties will not be restricted by this Privacy Policy with respect to their use and further sharing of your personal information. You may choose to opt-out of releasing your information to third parties as described in section 11 below.

From time to time we may offer links to third party sites on our site. Again by linking through to and using these websites and/or applications you become subject to the third parties' privacy policies, so please read the third party sites' privacy policies before submitting personal or other information or using the applications.

### 5\. Online Advertising, Third Party Advertisers and Analytics

We may share your information, including non-personal information or information that has been de-identified, as well as a record of any transactions you conduct on our website or offline with us, with third-party advertising partners (including network advertisers, ad agencies, and analytics companies) and their service providers in order to provide us with information regarding traffic on our website, deliver advertising tailored to your interests when you visit this or other websites and applications and to provide us with information regarding the use of our website and the effectiveness of our advertisements.

In connection with serving content and providing analytics and advertisement services, third parties may collect certain information about your visits to our or other websites. These third parties may set and access their own tracking technologies such as cookies and may otherwise collect or have access to your IP address, browser type, type of device you use to access our website and domain name from which you arrived at our website, device identifier, location-data, and specific web pages on our website through which you click, among other information. We may share device identifier, de-personalized information, usage information and similar information about visitors with third-party advertising companies, analytics providers, and other vendors for similar purposes.

Tracking technologies, including those set by third-party network advertisers, may be used to, among other things, target advertisements, prevent you from seeing the same advertisements too many times and to conduct research regarding the usefulness of certain advertisements to you. Some of the of service providers we use to perform advertising services may be members of the Network Advertising Initiative ("NAI") or the Digital Advertising Alliance ("DAA") Self-Regulatory Program for Online Behavioral Advertising. You may want to visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>, which provides information regarding targeted advertising and the "opt-out" procedures of NAI members. You may also want to visit <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>, which provides information regarding targeted advertising and offers an "opt-out" by participating companies in the DAA Self-Regulatory Program. Please note opting out through these mechanisms does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads while online.

In addition, we set our own cookie in coordination with our online advertising vendor Conversant, LLC. (and its service providers) to assist us in determining which of our offers and advertisements to serve you on our site or elsewhere online. To opt-out of this cookie [click here](http://dtmc.shopjustice.com/adinfo/choice/prod/?type=fpc&cid=3270&cname=Justice&cmagic=3f7bcd&clogo=3270.png&loc=us&lang=en-us). Please note that this is a cookie-based opt-out, so if you clear/delete the cookies on your device and/or browser, you may need to opt back out using the link above.

### 6\. How We Respond To “Do Not Track” Signals

**Some Internet browsers may be configured to send “Do Not Track” signals to the online services that you visit. There is no consensus among industry participants as to what “Do Not Track” means in this context. Like many websites and online services, our site does not alter its practices when it receives a “Do Not Track” signal from a visitor’s browser. To find out more about “Do Not Track,” please visit[http://www.allaboutdnt.com](http://www.allaboutdnt.com/)**

### 7\. Information You Disclose Publicly on our Sites.

Our sites may offer message boards, chat rooms, and other public areas (collectively, "Community Forums") where you can engage in social networking, interact with others, as well as have the opportunity to submit photographs, writings, music, video, audio recordings, computer graphics, pictures, data, questions, comments, suggestions or other content, including personal information (collectively, "User Submissions"). To participate in Community Forums, you may be asked to select a username and password. Please do not use your (or anyone else's) real name as your username.

Note that anything you post to a Community Forum is public. Information you post or make available in the Community Forums may be viewed, collected or used by others. The restrictions in this Privacy Policy do not apply to your disclosure of information in Community Forums. Think carefully before you post and use caution before disclosing any Personal Information.

User Submissions may be published online or offline in any media or format (currently existing or hereafter developed). We may also publish your name, voice, likeness and other personal information with your User Submissions, and we may use the content, or any portion of the content, for advertising, marketing, publicity and promotional activities. For full terms and conditions regarding User Submissions you submit to our Community Forums, please review our [Terms of Use](http://www.shopjustice.com/customer-service/terms-of-use).

### 8\. Information We Receive from Third Parties.

We may receive information about you from third parties. For example, if you are on another website and you opt-in to receive information from Justice, that website will forward to us your email address and other information about you so that we may contact you as requested. You may also choose to participate in a third party application or feature (such as one of our Facebook applications or a similar application or feature on a third party website) through which you allow us to collect (or the third party to share) information about you, including personal information. The third party may allow you to remove the application or feature, in which case we will no longer collect information about you through the application or feature, but we may retain the information previously collected.

In addition, we may receive information about you if other users of a third party website give us access to their profiles and you are one of their "connections" or information about you is otherwise accessible through your "connections'" web page, profile page, or similar page on a social networking or other third party website or interactive service. We will not use information we collect solely through a "connection" for marketing purposes without consent.

We may also supplement the information we collect about you with outside records from third parties in order to enhance our ability to serve you, to tailor our content to you and to offer you opportunities to purchase products or services that we believe may be of interest to you.

### 9\. Contracted Companies that Facilitate Communications and Transactions With You.

We may hire companies to help deliver products or services, like a shipping company that delivers a package, or who may provide support for the internal operations or websites of our companies, or a company that helps fulfillment for online product orders. In those instances, there is a need to share your information with these contracted companies, but they in turn do not disclose or use that information for any other purpose. Your opt-out choices below will not apply to sharing of your information by us with any of these companies. **Note: our contracted companies are contractually bound to maintain the confidentiality and security of all customer information.**

### 10\. Disclosure Required by Law and to Help Protect the Security and Safety of Our Websites.

Regardless of any opt-out choices that you make under 9 below, we will disclose personal information when we believe in good faith that such disclosures (a) are required by law, including a court order or subpoena, or (b) will help to: enforce contest, sweepstakes, promotions, and/or game rules; protect your (c) safety or security; and/or, (d) protect the safety and security of our websites.

### 11\. Choices You Have About the Collection, Use and Sharing of your Personal Information.

With regard to personal information that you have provided under this Privacy Policy, there are several opt-out choices available to you. These opt-out choices are the means by which you give us, or decline to give us, your consent to use your personal information for the purposes covered by these opt-out choices.

Your three opt-out choices are:

(i). Third Parties: You may choose to opt out of receiving promotional materials from third parties and if so we will not release your personal information to them. If you do not choose this opt-out, we may release your personal information as set forth in Section 4 so that third parties can send you promotional communications and materials.

(ii). Tween Brands and Affiliated Companies: You may choose to opt-out of receiving promotional materials from any of the Tween Brands companies and its affiliated companies, including Justice. In doing so, you may choose to opt-out of receiving all promotional materials delivered to you OR designate communications of a specific manner, such as postal mail, email, or voice-messaging.

(iii). Complete Customer Opt-out: You may choose to opt-out of receiving promotional materials from all of the Tween Brands companies, its affiliated companies, and third parties.

Please keep in mind that any opt-out choices you make will not apply in situations where (a) you later make a specific request for information from us; (b) we use your personal information for either operational uses or fulfillment uses (as described above); or (c) we share your personal information under the provisions above with respect to "Contracted Companies That Facilitate Transactions with You, and "Disclosures Required by Law and to Help Protect the Security and Safety of Our Websites."

There are several methods by which you can exercise your opt-out choices: (a) sending a written request via email to: [privacy@tweenbrands.com](mailto:privacy@tweenbrands.com) and by writing "Privacy Policy" in the subject line; (b) sending a written request via postal mail to: Justice Privacy Policy, 8323 Walton Parkway, New Albany, OH 43054 or (c) telephone 1-866-246-5822 and press the Customer Service option key to leave a message for our privacy policy team. Regardless of which method you choose, please be sure to indicate your opt-out choice. Finally, you may unsubscribe from certain email communications by clicking on unsubscribe links in those emails.

### 12\. California Residents.

Under California law, you may make a written request to us about how we have shared your information with contracted partners for our direct marketing purposes and other third parties for their direct marketing purposes. In response to your written request, we may provide you with a notice describing the cost-free means to opt-out of our direct marketing promotions and/or other third party information sharing. There are two methods by which you can make this request: (a) sending a written request via email to: [privacy@tweenbrands.com](mailto:privacy@tweenbrands.com) and by writing "Privacy Policy" in the subject line; or (b) sending a written request via postal mail to: Justice Privacy Policy, 8323 Walton Parkway, New Albany, OH 43054.

### 13\. Privacy Policy Questions.

If you have questions or wish to send us comments, you can let us know by sending us an email at [privacy@tweenbrands.com](mailto:privacy@tweenbrands.com) and writing "Privacy Policy" in the subject line, or by writing to us at: Justice Privacy Policy, 8323 Walton Parkway, New Albany, OH 43054.

Customers may also contact 1-866-246-5822 and press the appropriate option key to leave a message for our Privacy Policy team.

### 14\. Security of Our Website.

We use reasonable administrative, technical, personnel and physical measures to safeguard your personal information in its possession against loss, theft and unauthorized use, disclosure or modification. All information is stored behind firewalls. Credit information is encrypted both in transit and when stored with online databases.

Thank you for reading our Privacy Policy. We may change our policy from time to time. If we make any material changes in the way we collect, use, and/or share your personal information, we will notify you by prominently posting notice of the changes on our websites covered by this Privacy Policy.

Use of our websites signifies your acceptance of the terms of this Privacy Policy.
